Jahanvi Sharma

Student

I am a tech enthusiast who love to write code and working on new technologies. I have participated in many Coding Legacy on Coding Platforms. I am also interested in Research and Patents. I am a quick learner with Innovative Thinking and knowing languages like English, Hindi, Punjabi.



jahanvisharma125@gmail.com 🔀

7986680919

BLOCK 9 , QUATER NO. 197 GOVENMENT QUATERS, GHALORI GATE PATIALA, Patiala, India

09 June, 2001 🛗

jahanvisharma.ml/

linkedin.com/in/jahanvi-sharma in

github.com/jahanvisharma-dotcom 🕥

EDUCATION:

Bachelors Of Computer Science Engineering

Chandigarh University, Mohali

2019 - Present

Diploma in Computer Science EngineeringThapar Institute of Engineering and
Technology

2016 - 2019

First Division With Hons.

Intermediate (12th)

Children Memorial Sr. Sec. Public School

2019 70%

Matriculation

National High School, Patiala

2016 75%

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Technical Sketch Artist

Innovator's Hub, Chandigarh University

09/2020 - Present

Student Partner

Internshala

11/2020 - Present

Event Coordinator

Department of Students Welfare , Chandigarh University

09/2019 - Present

Campus Ambassador

Global Skills Summit (IEEE, DELHI)

2020

Campus Ninja

Coding Ninjas

2020 - Present

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

CAR ACCIDENT DETECTOR AND INFORMER (09/2020 - Present)

 The accident notification System notifies or informs about the accident spot, time to the nearby hospital, police station and family members. Of course, this project has very high priority in order because will save life in road accident.

REAL TIME EMOTION DETECTION USING KERAS (06/2020 - 10/2020)

 A project to detect natural human emotions in real time as well as in image also for eg: happy face, sad face, angry face etc. Used Technologies: - ML • Open CV • Python • Keras • Tensorflow.

SHOINE (02/2020 - 05/2020)

 An Online Shopping Website Used for Shopping of Electronics, Garments etc, This Website contains Chat Bot to Help you for find better product. Technologies Used: Frontent + Backend Web development

HEY PEOPLE (06/2018 - 07/2018)

 A windows based Chat applcation using Microsoft Visual Studio C#, Based on IP ADDRESSING (two clients can comminicate with each other using IP addresses.

CERTIFICATES

Web Development - INTERNSHALA (04/2020 - 06/2020)

White Hat Hacker And Pen Tester (08/2020)

Cloud Engineering Badage - GOOGLE CLOUD (10/2020)

Data Science And Machine Learning Badage - GOOGLE CLOUD (10/2020)

AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials (11/2020)

AWS Training and Certification